<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-14T13:48:29-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Timeliners</title><subtitle>A watch company who has been in the town for so many years with very deep expereience in watch sell.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">New Rolex</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/men%20watches/2018/08/18/newRolex.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Rolex" /><published>2018-08-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-08-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/men%20watches/2018/08/18/new-rolex</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/men%20watches/2018/08/18/newRolex.html">&lt;p&gt;
	Hur Makes Leap in the Rankings
	Sunday, Mi Jung Hur returned to the winner’s circle for the first time in five years with her victory at the Aberdeen Standard Investments Ladies Scottish Open. With her victory, she jumped 36 spots in the Rolex Rankings, moving from 79 to 43 in the world. Over the last five years, Hur has taken a ride up and down the rankings. In August 2017, she climbed to a career high No. 15 in the world as she recorded one of her most consistent seasons on Tour with six top 10s. But Hur didn’t record a single top 10 in 2018 and dropped as low as No. 121 in the world before rebounding in 2019 with two top 10s and a victory through the first eight months of the year.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Ko In the Hunt For Season's Biggest Awards
	Jin Young Ko skipped last week’s event in Scotland following an incredible stretch that saw her record three consecutive top-3 finishes, including a major victory at the Evian Championship. Although she didn’t tee it up last week, she still maintains her hold on the Tour’s biggest awards heading into the final stretch of the year. Ko sits atop the money list, the Race to the CME Globe point standings, the Rolex Player of the Year race and she leads the Tour in scoring. She’s also ranked No. 1 in G.I.R. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Rookie Jeongeun Lee6 is putting on quite a show in her first season on Tour. She not only leads the Louise Suggs Rolex Player of the Year race, she also sits No. 2 behind Ko on the money list, the Race to the CME Globe point standings and the Rolex Player of the Year race. She’s also ranked No. 4 on Tour in scoring average.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
	&quot;I just can’t believe anything like that could happen,&quot; he said.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
		The top 5 in the Solheim Cup point standings - Lexi Thompson, Nelly Korda, Danielle Kang, Lizette Salas and Jessica Korda – secured their position on Team USA in recent weeks. Monday, Marina Alex and Megan Khang secured their spot on the team via the Solheim Cup point standings, which means the eighth and final spot is the only remaining position to be determined following the CP Women’s Open. Brittany Altomare sits at No. 8 in the standings with 257.50 points, Ally McDonald is at No. 9 with 250.50 points and Cristie Kerr is No. 10 with 224.50 points. Players competing in Canada must finish inside the top 10 in order to earn points, with as many as 60 points going to the winner. Click here for the complete standings.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Content Reference : &lt;a href=&quot;https://articlegenerator.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Article Generator&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Scott Roman</name></author><category term="Men" /><category term="Style" /><category term="Fashion" /><category term="Rolex" /><category term="Latest" /><summary type="html">Hur Makes Leap in the Rankings Sunday, Mi Jung Hur returned to the winner’s circle for the first time in five years with her victory at the Aberdeen Standard Investments Ladies Scottish Open. With her victory, she jumped 36 spots in the Rolex Rankings, moving from 79 to 43 in the world. Over the last five years, Hur has taken a ride up and down the rankings. In August 2017, she climbed to a career high No. 15 in the world as she recorded one of her most consistent seasons on Tour with six top 10s. But Hur didn’t record a single top 10 in 2018 and dropped as low as No. 121 in the world before rebounding in 2019 with two top 10s and a victory through the first eight months of the year.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Renovated Store</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/news/2018/05/22/renovatedStore.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Renovated Store" /><published>2018-05-22T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-05-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/news/2018/05/22/renovated-store</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/news/2018/05/22/renovatedStore.html">&lt;p&gt;
	BOULDER, Colo., Aug. 12, 2019 /PRNewswire/ -- Renovation Brands, the parent company of multiple fast growing home improvement product brands, announced today the closing of its latest acquisition, DecorPlanet.com. DecorPlanet is a leading, fast growing omni-channel provider in the home and bathroom products space. They specialize in decorative plumbing and hardware, kitchen sinks, faucets and lighting. Products are sold on DecorPlanet.com, as well as through wholesale relationships and four showrooms in the New York City area. In addition to its proprietary Fresca brand, they offer hundreds of other internationally recognized third-party brands.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	(PRNewsfoto/Renovation Brands)
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
	&quot;We are thrilled to welcome Robert Gavartin and the DecorPlanet team to the Renovation Brands family.  In addition to our existing online ready to assemble kitchen cabinet brand, RTA Cabinet Store (RTAcabinetstore.com), DecorPlanet provides us with an extremely strong digital footprint in the growing multi-billion dollar Kitchen &amp; Bath space,&quot; said Marc Sieger, CEO of Renovation Brands. &quot;DecorPlanet is a big step forward in positioning Renovation Brands as a leading player in the growing online home improvement and renovation market.&quot;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
	&quot;We are equally excited to be part of the Renovation Brands and Digital Fuel Capital family. We were looking for the right partner with the digital, analytical, and operational chops who could help take our business to the next level and meet the future needs of our customers and employees. I am happy to say, we found a great fit,&quot; said Robert Gavartin, President of DecorPlanet.com.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Houlihan Lokey served as financial advisor to Renovation Brands and Aramar Capital Group, LLC served as financial advisor to DecorPlanet on this acquisition.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;
		About Renovation Brands:
	&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Renovation Brands is the parent company of multiple fast growing home improvement product brands serving both residential and commercial customers in the renovation space. With a distinct focus and competence in the digital space, Renovation Brands is a top 500 e-retailer that is owned by Digital Fuel Capital, a leader in investing in internet retail and digital marketing technology and services.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Renovation Brands is currently comprised of nine specialty eCommerce brands including American Tin Ceilings, Reggio Register, Electric Fireplaces Direct, Mantels Direct, Electric Fireplaces Canada, Electric Heat Source, Baseboarders, RTA Cabinet Store, and DecorPlanet.com.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Content Source: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/renovation-brands-acquires-decorplanetcom-a-leading-omni-channel-provider-in-the-home-and-bathroom-products-space-300900102.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;PRNewswire&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Content Reference : &lt;a href=&quot;https://articlegenerator.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Article Generator&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Robert Pearson</name></author><category term="Timeliners" /><category term="Store" /><category term="Latest" /><summary type="html">BOULDER, Colo., Aug. 12, 2019 /PRNewswire/ -- Renovation Brands, the parent company of multiple fast growing home improvement product brands, announced today the closing of its latest acquisition, DecorPlanet.com. DecorPlanet is a leading, fast growing omni-channel provider in the home and bathroom products space. They specialize in decorative plumbing and hardware, kitchen sinks, faucets and lighting. Products are sold on DecorPlanet.com, as well as through wholesale relationships and four showrooms in the New York City area. In addition to its proprietary Fresca brand, they offer hundreds of other internationally recognized third-party brands.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Opening</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/news/2017/04/15/newOpening.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Opening" /><published>2017-04-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-04-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/news/2017/04/15/new-opening</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/http://localhost:3000/blogs/news/2017/04/15/newOpening.html">&lt;p&gt;
	This week, the United States and Turkey achieved a significant breakthrough. After many months of negotiations, the two countries agreed to coordinate on a joint buffer zone in northern Syria. This development offers a rare and fleeting opportunity for President Trump to step back from the brink of disaster. The president can salvage his Syria policy by making clear the United States will stick around to defend its vital national interests there.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	Ever since Trump announced by tweet last December that he was withdrawing all U.S. troops from Syria, without consulting most of his military commanders, the United States’ Syria strategy — especially in the northeast — has been a muddle. To his credit, the president partially walked back the decision, announcing in February that a small, residual force would remain to keep the Islamic State down, keep our partnership with the Kurds and keep an eye on Iranian forces.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	But the U.S.-Turkey rift, pushed to the breaking point by Turkish threats to unilaterally invade northeast Syria, risks turning that ambiguous U.S. policy into a total failure. If the Turks invade, the Kurds might ally with Syrian President Bashar al-Assad, to the advantage of Iran and the Islamic State. Any remaining U.S. leverage to push for an acceptable political solution would vanish.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	After months of scant progress, the State Department announced Wednesday that Turkey and the United States agreed to coordinate establishment of a safe zone on the Syrian side of the border as a “peace corridor,” starting with a joint operations center inside Turkey to work out the details.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
	“The plan is for U.S. troops to work to patrol with Turkish forces to ensure security in the safe zone,” a senior State Department official told me, cautioning that the details aren’t final. “By strengthening U.S.-Turkish cooperation in the one area of the Syria conflict where we were at odds, this agreement also advances broader U.S. objectives for a resolution of the Syria conflict.”
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	If the United States wants to have any influence over what happens next in Syria, it will need to resolve its rift with Turkey, which has complex and serious causes. The Syrian Kurds, our allies whom we armed to fight the Islamic State, must be assured that Turkish forces won’t slaughter them. The Turks must be assured that the Kurds will withdraw from the border. We are not there yet. But this interim statement is a crucial step in the right direction.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
		Content Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/global-opinions/theres-a-new-opening-for-trump-to-avoid-disaster-in-syria/2019/08/08/637d6efc-ba18-11e9-a091-6a96e67d9cce_story.html?noredirect=on&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kim Matthew</name></author><category term="Timeliners" /><category term="Store" /><category term="Latest" /><summary type="html">This week, the United States and Turkey achieved a significant breakthrough. After many months of negotiations, the two countries agreed to coordinate on a joint buffer zone in northern Syria. This development offers a rare and fleeting opportunity for President Trump to step back from the brink of disaster. The president can salvage his Syria policy by making clear the United States will stick around to defend its vital national interests there.</summary></entry></feed>